http://www.christchurchatl.org/privacy-policy/

Christ Church of AtlantaHomeAbout UsOur MissionChildren’s MinistryFamily Life MinistryMusic MinistryYouth MinistryParticipateEventsPrayer RequestsVolunteerDonateMediaSermonsSermons (2020)Sermons (2019)Sermons (2018)Sermons (2017)Sermons (2016)Sermons (2015)Sermons (2014)Sermons (2013)Sunday School LessonsSunday School Lessons (2020)Sunday School Lessons (2019)Sunday School Lessons (2018)Sunday School Lessons (2017)Sunday School Lessons (2016)Sunday School Lessons (2015)Sunday School Lessons (2014)Alfred’s NewslettersJan’s NewslettersGalleryContactGive
Last updated: 5/24/2019OverviewThis privacy policy will advise you about our guidelines concerning the use of your personal information, including, without limitation, the reasonable efforts we make to protect your personal information in accordance with these guidelines, and about what choices you have concerning our use of such information. Please read this policy carefully. We may need to change this policy from time to time in order to address new issues and reflect changes on our Site. We will post those changes here so that you will always know our policies regarding what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose that information to anyone. Please refer back to this policy regularly.We keep your private information private by:Not selling your information—You’ve entrusted us with your personal information, and we’re committed to using it wisely. Christ Church of Atlanta will not sell your personal information to anyone, for any reason, at any time.Using firewalls and encryption—We use firewalls and encryption technology to protect personal information on our computer systems.Restricting who has access to your information—We take precautions to ensure that your internet account and personal information are accessible only by relevant parties who are authorized to have access to your personal information.If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please contact our Data Security Officer at:Christ Church of Atlantainfo@christchurchatl.orgScope of Privacy PolicyThis policy applies to your use of this site. This policy does not apply to your use of unaffiliated sites to which this site only links.Personal Identification Information and UseWe may request personal identification information from you (such as your last name, business, phone, address) in connection with your use of, or participation in registration for surveys, forums, content submissions, chats, bulletin boards, discussion groups,requests for suggestions, participation in emails and newsletters, for physical content delivery or additional information, and in connection with other activities, services or resources we make available on any of our website. In all of these cases, we will collect personal identification information from you only if you voluntarily submit such information to us. Except as otherwise provided in this policy, we reasonably endeavor to ensure that we never intentionally disclose any personal identification information about you as an individual user to any third party without having received your permission (through opt-in or similar procedures) except as provided for herein or otherwise as permitted or required under law. Further, Christ Church of Atlanta may contact you based on the information you provide online whether in connection with your registration or in such places as the above described forums.If you do provide us with personal information for any of these activities, we may use it to conduct the activity.Christ Church of Atlanta does not rent or sell personal identification information to outside marketers. In certain circumstances, Christ Church of Atlanta may share personal identification information with trusted service providers that need access to your information to provide operational or other support services or we may share this aggregate statistical information with other third parties; to ensure the confidentiality and security of this information, service providers must agree to safeguard all information in strict compliance with our policy. We may also provide information to regulatory authorities and law enforcement officials in accordance with applicable law or when we otherwise believe in good faith that the law requires it.Non-Personal Identification InformationWe may collect non-personal identification information without limitation, through the use of the following types of methodology:“Cookie” technology: A “cookie” is an element of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system.“IP address tracking”: An IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer when you are on the Internet. When you request pages from our Sites, our servers log your IP address.“Web beacons”: A Web beacon, or “clear gif,” is a small graphic image on a webpage or web-based document that a website can use to determine information about a user.Non-personal identification information might include the browser you use, the type of computer, technical information about your means of connection to our websites (such as the operating systems and the Internet service providers utilized), and other similar information. Our systems may also automatically gather information about the areas you visit and search terms you utilize on our website and about the links you may select from within our website to other areas of the World Wide Web or elsewhere online.We use such information for our business purposes, and, in particular, primarily to administer the website, and, in the aggregate, to what technologies are being used so that we may continually improve our Site.“Do Not Track” DisclosuresOur website honors your browser security and privacy settings. For some browsers, you can change and turn off tracking features and other security settings in your browser.In addition, Google Analytics offers an Opt-out Browser Add-on. Google provides a free add-on to most major browsers that you can install to prevent your data from being collected and used by Google Analytics. To learn more and obtain the Opt-out Browser Add-on visit https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.Privacy of ChildrenWe are mindful that young people need special safeguards and privacy protection. We realize that they may not understand all the provisions of our policy or be able to make thoughtful decisions about the choices that are made available to our adult users. We strongly urge all parents to participate in their children’s exploration of the Internet and any online services, and to teach their children about protecting their personal information while online.Christ Church of Atlanta does not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen (13) without verifiable parental consent. If it is determined that such information has been inadvertently collected on anyone under the age of thirteen (13), we shall immediately take the necessary steps to ensure that such information is deleted from our system’s database. Anyone under the age of thirteen (13) must seek and obtain parent or guardian permission to use this website.Community GuidelinesWe want to hear from you on social media, our blogs, and our forums but have a few things that we do not allow posts that contain, discuss or promote:abusive, vulgar, offensive, threatening or harassing languagepersonal attacks of any kindillegal activitypolitical campaignslegal or employment issuesConversations that negatively target specific individuals or groupsPosts that are spam, solicitations or advertisementsContest and voting campaign posts that are not authorized by Christ Church of AtlantaAny profile icon or name related to commercial content that promotes another business, website, specialty page other than our organization or those approved by usPersonally identifiable information (like phone numbers or email addresses), private or sensitive details about another personMaterial or information that you don’t have the right to post or shareAdditional rules for blog comments and forums:No profanity or skirting the language filter.No political or religious issues.No posting of premium content from any website.No trolling or posting of fake news.Use of descriptive thread titles.Differences of opinion are welcome as long as they are respectful. Be courteous and respect those asking questions with friendly, informative discussions. If it’s not, it will be deleted. Posters will be permanently banned immediately for a serious, willful, and/or repeated violation of any of these rules.User-submitted content (including comments, updates, photos and videos) do not necessarily represent the views of Christ Church of Atlanta.The statements and opinions posted by registered participants to these forums and blogs on our website are offered for educational, informational, and social purposes only, should not be construed as providing advice of any kind.Some links featured on our website, social media, blogs, and forums will take you to non-Christ Church of Atlanta websites. The views and opinions of authors expressed on those websites do not necessarily state or reflect those of Christ Church of Atlanta.Links to Other SitesUsers will find other content on our website that link to the sites and services of other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies, or no policy (policies) at all. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any third-party sites or services before providing any of them with your personal information.Access and CorrectionWith some exceptions designed to protect the rights of others or in respect of security, you have the right to a copy of the personal data that we hold about you. We may make a reasonable charge for additional copies of that data beyond the first copy, based on our administrative costs. Where the data is data that you have given to us, you have the right to receive your copy of it in a common electronic format, and to provide copies of it to other people if you wish.You have the right to have the personal data we hold about you corrected if it is factually inaccurate. This right does not extend to matters of opinion, such as company-specific annotations on your account/information.Choice/Opt-Out/DELETIONIf we are processing your personal data on the basis of your consent, you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time, in which case we will stop that processing unless we have another legal basis on which to continue.You have the right to have personal data that we hold about you erased (the right “to be forgotten”). This right is not generally available where we still have a valid legal reason to keep the data (for example, for security reasons or because we are obliged to do so by law). You should be aware, however, that it is not always possible to completely remove or modify information in our databases and servers, although we will always make reasonable efforts to do so upon your request, and we are unable to have your information removed from the records of any third party who has been provided with your information in accordance with this policy.The easiest method of exercising your rights as set out above is to:Email our Data Protection Officer at info@christchurchatl.org orPlease note that in order to protect your privacy, we may ask you to prove your identity before we take any steps in response to a request you have made.Opting Out of MarketingYou have the right to require us to stop using your personal data to send you marketing information. If you want us to stop sending you marketing information, the quickest and most efficient way is to use the provided “unsubscribe” links in our communications (although you can contact us directly if you prefer).Consent to TransferThe website is operated in the United States. If you are located outside of the United States, please be aware that any information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. By using our Website, participating in any of our services and/or providing us with your information, you consent to this transfer.Your Acceptance of These TermsBy using our website, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Policy, your promise to comply with the representations you make and contained in the Privacy Policy and Terms of Use, and your understanding of the scope and limitations of the protections provided under the Privacy Policy and Terms of Use. If you do not agree to these policies, please do not use our website. Your continued use of the website following the posting of changes to these terms will mean that you accept those changes.Further Questions and ContactsIf you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, if you wish to exercise any of your rights in relation to your personal information, or if you want to object to the collection or processing of your data by Christ Church of Atlanta, whether entirely or partially, please contact our Data Protection Officer who can be reached at info@christchurchatl.org.
Search for:
CalendarDecember 2020SMTWTFS 12345678910111213141516171819202122232425262728293031  « Dec    © 2020 Christ Church of Atlanta, All Rights Reserved | Privacy PolicyContact / LocationContact infoChurch Office: 6059 Boylston Drive, NE, Atlanta, GA 303286059 Boylston Drive, NE, Atlanta, GA 30328 Phone: 404.255.5033 Fax: 404.255.5033 Email: info@christchurchatl.org Mailing Address: PO Box 76320, Atlanta, GA 30358Gathering TimesSunday: 9:30 AM - Sunday School 10:30 AM - Traditional ServiceFor additional information regarding our Sunday services, including parking information, please contact us. May you come to Know, Grow and Proclaim Jesus.Events / CalendarUpcoming EventsSun, 12/13 10:30 AM3rd Sunday in AdventSun, 12/20 10:30 AM4th Sunday in AdventThu, 12/24 8:00 AMChristmas EveFri, 12/25 8:00 AMChristmas DaySun, 12/27 10:30 AM1st Sunday of Christmas
